<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FLover</string>
    //Rose

    <string name="ToolsForFlowerRose">
\nPruning shears
\nSprayer or hose for watering
\nGloves
\nProtective agents against pests and diseases
\nFertilizers</string>
    <string name="StepsFlowerRose">
        \n1.Plant the roses in a sunny location with well-drained soil.
\n2.Water the roses deeply
        and regularly, especially during hot weather.
\n3.Apply a balanced fertilizer to the soil around the roses in early spring.
\n4.Prune the roses in late winter or early spring to remove dead wood and shape the plant.
\n5.Monitor the roses for pests and diseases and treat them promptly if necessary.
\n6.Mulch the soil around the roses to retain moisture and suppress weed growth.
\n7.Deadhead the roses by removing spent blooms to encourage new growth and repeat flowering.
\n8.Monitor the roses for signs of stress, such as wilting or yellowing leaves, and adjust care as needed.
\n9.Protect the roses from harsh winter weather by covering them with burlap or another protective material.</string>


    //Tulip
    <string name="ToolsForFlowerTulip">
        \nWatering can or sprayer
\nTray for water collection and tray with stones or gravel
\nLighting fixtures
\nSoil and mulch
\nFertilizers pest and disease control.</string>
    <string name="StepsFlowerTulip">
       \n1.Planting - Choose a sunny location with well-drained soil. Plant tulip bulbs in the fall,about 6 8 weeks before the first frost. Plant the bulbs with the pointed end up, and cover with soil.
\n2.Watering - Tulips need regular watering to keep their soil moist, but not soggy.Water the plants deeply when the top inch of soil feels dry to the touch.
\n3.Fertilizing - Fertilize the tulip plants once a month during the growing season with fertilizer. Avoid over fertilizing, as this can lead to weak stems and foliage.
\n4.Pruning - Remove faded flowers and leaves as they appear. Once the tulip plant has finished blooming,cut off the stem at the base to encourage the bulb to store energy for next years growth.
\n5.Pests and Diseases - Keep an eye out for pests and diseases such as aphids, and fungal infections. Use organic insecticides and fungicides as necessary.
\n6Winter Care - Tulips are dormant during winter, and need to be protected from freezing temperatures.Cover the soil around the tulip plants with a layer of mulch to protect the bulbs.
</string>


    //Peonies
    <string name="ToolsForFlowerPeonies">
        \nPruning Shears
\nPruning Shears
\nFertilizer
\nSoil Moisture Meter
\nPot with Drainage Holes.
    </string>
    <string name="StepsFlowerPeonies">
        \n1.Planting - Choose a location with well drained soil and
        full sun to plant your peonies. Plant the peony roots in the fall or early spring,
        making sure to place them at the right depth and spacing.
\n2.Watering - Peonies need regular watering to keep their soil moist,
        but not soggy. Water the plants deeply when the top inch of soil feels dry to the touch.
\n3.Fertilizing - Fertilize the peony plants in the spring and again after they finish blooming
        with a balanced fertilizer. Avoid fertilizing during hot, dry weather to prevent stressing the plant.
\n4.Pruning - Prune back dead or damaged stems and leaves in the fall, and cut off any faded flowers after they bloom in the spring.
        Leave the foliage in place after blooming, as it provides energy to the plant for next years growth.
\n5.Pest and Disease Control - Keep an eye out for pests and diseases such as spider mites,
        and fungal infections. Use organic insecticides and fungicides as necessary.
\n6.Winter Care - Peonies are dormant during winter and need to be protected from freezing temperatures.
        Cover the soil around the peony plants with a layer of mulch to protect the roots.

    </string>



    //Lilie
    <string name="ToolsForFlowerLilie">Pot
\nSoil
\nFertilizer
\nWatering
\nPruning shears
\nSupport stakes</string>
    <string name="StepsFlowerLilie">1.Watering: Lilies prefer consistently moist but not waterlogged soil,
        so water them regularly. Allow the top inch of soil to dry out slightly between waterings,
        but do not let the soil become bone dry.
\n2.Soil: Use a well-draining, nutrient-rich potting mix for your potted lilies.
      The soil should be slightly acidic with a pH level between 5.5 and 6.5.
\n3.Fertilizing: Fertilize your lilies with a slow-release fertilizer in the spring,
        or use a liquid fertilizer that is high in phosphorus to encourage flower production.
\n4.Sunlight: Lilies require plenty of sunlight to grow and bloom,
        so place them in a spot where they can receive at least six hours of direct sunlight each day.
\n5.Temperature: Lilies prefer cooler temperatures and will not do well in hot,
        dry environments. Keep your lilies in a room that is between 60-75°F (15-24°C).
\n6.Humidity: Lilies appreciate high humidity levels, so consider placing
        a humidifier near your plants or misting them regularly.
\n7.Pruning: Deadhead your lilies by removing spent flowers and seed pods to encourage new growth and prolong the blooming period.
        Prune back stems to the ground after the foliage has died back in the fall.</string>


    //Orchid
    <string name="ToolsForFlowerOrchid"> Pot
\nFertilizer
\nWatering can
\nPruning shears
\nSupport stakes
\nInsecticides and fungicides
</string>
    <string name="StepsFlowerOrchid">1.Watering: Orchids require consistent moisture but should never
        be allowed to sit in standing water. Water your orchid when the potting media is almost dry,
        and be sure to drain any excess water from the bottom of the pot.
\n2.Potting Media: Orchids require well-draining media to avoid waterlogged roots.
        Specialty orchid bark or sphagnum moss can provide the proper drainage.
\n3.Fertilizing: Orchids require regular fertilization to thrive.
        Use a balanced orchid fertilizer once a month during the growing season, following the manufacturers instructions.
\n4.Sunlight: Orchids require bright, indirect light to grow and bloom. Avoid direct sunlight, which can burn the leaves.
\n5.Temperature: Orchids prefer warm, humid conditions. Keep your orchid in a
        room with temperatures between 60-85°F (15-29°C) during the day and slightly cooler at night.
\n6.Humidity: Orchids require high humidity levels to thrive. Consider placing a
        humidifier near your plants, or use a tray of pebbles filled with water to increase humidity.
\n7.Pruning: Prune your orchid as needed to remove dead or damaged leaves or flowers. Remove any dead or dying roots.
\n8.Repotting: Orchids require occasional repotting as they outgrow their pots or the potting media becomes old and decomposed.
        Repot your orchid when the potting media is almost completely broken down, or every 1-2 years.
\n9.Pests and Diseases: Keep an eye out for pests such as spider mites, mealybugs, and scale insects. Orchids can also be susceptible
        to fungal diseases like root rot or bacterial infections. Treat any issues promptly with appropriate insecticides or fungicides.

    </string>


    //Violet
    <string name="ToolsForFlowerViolet">Pot
\nPlant support
\nScissors or pruning shears
\nFertilizer
\nPotting soil
\nInsecticides and fungicides</string>
    <string name="StepsFlowerViolet">1.Watering: Violets like to be kept moist but not waterlogged.
        Water them once a week or when the top inch of soil feels dry.
\n2.Light: Violets prefer bright, indirect light. They can also tolerate some
        direct sunlight in the morning or late afternoon, but too much can burn their leaves.
\n3.Temperature and Humidity: Violets like cool temperatures (between 60-70°F or 15-21°C)
        and high humidity. You can increase humidity by placing a tray of water near the plant or using a humidifier.
\n4. Soil: Use a well-draining soil mix that is specifically formulated for African violets.
\n5. Fertilizer: Feed violets with a balanced, water-soluble fertilizer every month during the growing season (spring and summer).
\n6. Pruning: Pinch off any dead or yellow leaves and spent blooms to encourage new growth.
\n7. Repotting: Repot violets every 6-12 months or when the pot becomes too small for the plant.
        Use a slightly larger pot and fresh soil mix.
\n8. Pest control: Watch out for pests such as aphids, spider mites, and mealybugs.
        If you notice any infestation, use an insecticidal soap or neem oil to treat the plant.
</string>


    //Chamomile
    <string name="ToolsForFlowerChamomile">Pot
\nSoil
\nWatering can
\nFertilizer
\nPruning shears
\nSunlight
\nHumidity</string>
    <string name="StepsFlowerChamomile"> 1.Planting: Chamomile plants prefer well-draining soil and full sun exposure.
        Plant the seeds or seedlings in a spot that gets at least 6 hours of sunlight per day.
\n2.Watering: Chamomile plants prefer consistent moisture but do not like to sit in wet soil.
        Water the plants deeply once or twice a week, depending on weather conditions and soil moisture.
\n3.Fertilizing: Chamomile plants do not require much fertilization, but you can add some compost or
        a balanced fertilizer once or twice a month during the growing season.
\n4.Pruning: Deadhead the spent blooms regularly to encourage more flowers to bloom.
        You can also trim back the plants by a third in midsummer to promote bushier growth.
\n5.Pests and Diseases: Chamomile plants are generally not bothered by pests or diseases, but keep an
        eye out for aphids, spider mites, and powdery mildew. If you notice any signs of
        infestation or disease, treat the plants with an appropriate insecticide or fungicide.
\n6.Harvesting: Harvest the flowers when they are fully open but before they start to fade.
        You can either dry the flowers for tea or use them fresh for aromatherapy or skincare purposes.
\n7. Winter Care: Chamomile plants are annuals or perennials depending on the variety. If you have perennial
        chamomile, cut back the plants in the fall and mulch heavily to protect them from freezing temperatures.</string>
</resources>
